<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-18T09:52:33+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">dr jack wilson.</title><subtitle>This website is a personal space for me to share my work in linguisitcs, pragmatics and gesture studies.  It is also a blog for sharing partially formed ideas. Criticisms are  welcome!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">introduction and practice</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/update/2020/06/17/first-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="introduction and practice" /><published>2020-06-17T09:13:38+01:00</published><updated>2020-06-17T09:13:38+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/update/2020/06/17/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/update/2020/06/17/first-post.html">&lt;html xmlns=&quot;http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml&quot; lang=&quot;&quot; xml:lang=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;head&gt;
  &lt;meta charset=&quot;utf-8&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;meta name=&quot;generator&quot; content=&quot;pandoc&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;meta name=&quot;viewport&quot; content=&quot;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0, user-scalable=yes&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;title&gt;introduction and practice&lt;/title&gt;
  &lt;style&gt;
      code{white-space: pre-wrap;}
      span.smallcaps{font-variant: small-caps;}
      span.underline{text-decoration: underline;}
      div.column{display: inline-block; vertical-align: top; width: 50%;}
  &lt;/style&gt;
  &lt;!--[if lt IE 9]&gt;
    &lt;script src=&quot;//cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/html5shiv/3.7.3/html5shiv-printshiv.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
  &lt;![endif]--&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;
&lt;body&gt;
&lt;header id=&quot;title-block-header&quot;&gt;
&lt;h1 class=&quot;title&quot;&gt;introduction and practice&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;date&quot;&gt;2020-06-17 09:13:38 +0100&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/header&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to start a blog for publishing “ideas in progress”. This website is being generated using jekyll, and, since I am not adept at this kind of thing, I decided to post a first blog as a way to practice and to say something about what this blog is for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is about the different strands of my thinking and to put some of my ideas down in print before I submit them as abstracts. In recent years I have had a few papers rejected from conferences and I think that part of the problem is that I often find myself at the interface of disciplines. Here I can say what I want. The hope is that writing it down will make it better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My research focusses on the realtionship between linguistic pragmatics and gesture studies. I typically adopt a cognitive perspective on pragmatics &lt;span class=&quot;citation&quot; data-cites=&quot;bara2010cognitive&quot;&gt;(Bara 2010)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;references&quot; class=&quot;unnumbered&quot;&gt;references&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;refs&quot; class=&quot;references&quot; role=&quot;doc-bibliography&quot;&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;ref-bara2010cognitive&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bara, Bruno G. 2010. &lt;em&gt;Cognitive Pragmatics: The Mental Processes of Communication&lt;/em&gt;. MIT Press.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">introduction and practice introduction and practice 2020-06-17 09:13:38 +0100 I decided to start a blog for publishing “ideas in progress”. This website is being generated using jekyll, and, since I am not adept at this kind of thing, I decided to post a first blog as a way to practice and to say something about what this blog is for. This blog is about the different strands of my thinking and to put some of my ideas down in print before I submit them as abstracts. In recent years I have had a few papers rejected from conferences and I think that part of the problem is that I often find myself at the interface of disciplines. Here I can say what I want. The hope is that writing it down will make it better. My research focusses on the realtionship between linguistic pragmatics and gesture studies. I typically adopt a cognitive perspective on pragmatics (Bara 2010) references Bara, Bruno G. 2010. Cognitive Pragmatics: The Mental Processes of Communication. MIT Press.</summary></entry></feed>